孩子们  有时候你的感情会一帆风顺
Kids, sometimes your relationship goes so smoothly for so long
久到你以为一辈子都会那样
that you think it will be that way forever.
但那是不可能的
It never is.
我们刚刚第一次吵架
Well, we just had our first fight.
We had our first fight.
不会吧  你们为了什么吵?
Oh, no, what'd you fight about?
几个月前  我的建设事务所进行了 一件新大楼的设计案
A few months ago, my architecture firm was approached to design this new building...
那是在斯普肯的大型摩天楼
It's this big skyscraper in Spokane.
这对他的事务所来说是个大案子
It'd be a huge project for his firm.
如果我们拿不到那个案子 我们可能就会倒闭
And if we don't get it, we could go under.
当首席设计师在全体员工
So anyway, the head architect unveils his new design
面前发表了他的设计
to the whole company.
- 不会吧 - 不会吧
- No. - No.
是的
Yes.
所有的摩天楼看起来都像是...
All skyscrapers kind of look like a...
马修 那是栋78层 粉红大理石的高楼
Marshall, it's a 78-story pink marble tower
顶上还有一个圆顶
with a rounded top
正面还有两个球形通道
and two spherical entryways at the front.
全套都齐了嘛
Wow, so it's the whole package.
- 讲得好 - 谢谢
- Yeah, you did. - Had to.
伙计  如果他们要卖公寓 你可要帮我弄一套
Oh, dude, if they're selling condos, you got to get me in.
但不要给我柱型部分的
And don't give me the shaft.
- 讲得好 - 谢谢
- Yeah, you did. - Had to.
这也太搞笑了
It's a travesty.
那将会是城市的空中标志物
It's gonna define the skyline of the city.
如果是我的话 我肯定能设计出很棒的作品
If it was me, I could've designed something amazing.
结果我却花了12个小时 去设计飞檐
Instead, I'm spending 12 hours a day designing the cornices.
- 讲得好 - 这个不是笑话
- Yeah, you did. - That wasn't one.
老爸老妈的浪漫史 第二季 第四集
你和泰德吵了第一次架
So you and Ted had your first fight.
很明显  结局还不错 我意思是 你还能和我一起在这儿
It obviously ended well. I mean, you're here with me.
事实上  我们还没吵完
Actually, it didn't end at all.
我开始生气后  就来了这里
I started getting bummed out, so I came here.
我就是这样的
It's what I do.
我祖母去世的时候 我去烫了头发
When my grandma died, I got a perm.
一天听到两个悲剧
Ooh, two tragedies in one day.
事情是这样的 泰德已经不断抱怨
The thing is, Ted has been literally
他的工作好几个星期了
complaining about work nonstop for weeks.
所以我今天过去以后 真的受够了...
So, when I came over today, I was kind of done.
- Hey. - Hey.
- 今天怎么样? - 很好
- How was your day? - Good.
你真是个好记者
Wow, you're a great interviewer.
你不准备问问我的工作吗?
Aren't you gonna ask how my day was?
不  我知道你过得很糟
No, I know how it was. It was awful.
今晚你想租部电影看看吗?
Ooh, you want to rent a movie tonight?
知道吗
You know, um...
我一直都倾听你工作上的事
I listen to your work stories all the time.
对  但是... 我不想显得太粗鲁
Yeah, but... and I don't want to be rude here,
但是我的故事都很有趣
but my work stories are interesting.
我是个电视新闻记者
I'm a television news reporter.
- 罗宾 - 怎么?
- Robin... - What?
我清楚知道他想说的话
I knew exactly what he was going to say.
我只是加快他的进程
I was just helping him get there faster.
你应该在自杀热线工作
You should work at a suicide hotline.
然后事情就变糟了
And then it got ugly.
我可没有把相同的故事 一遍又一遍跟你说
What I don't do is tell you the same story over and over again.
就像你也不会一部电影
I mean, you wouldn't watch the same movie
重复看很多次吧
over and over again, would you?
除非是像 虎胆龙威 那样的好电影
Maybe a great movie like Die Hard.
但如果是  梦幻之地?
But Field of Dreams?
看一次都嫌够了
Once is more than enough.
那就是你认为的糟糕电影?
So that's your go-to bad movie?
你所能想到的头号 糟糕电影的例子
The number one example on the tip of your tongue
梦幻之地?
of a bad movie is Field of Dreams?
那部电影是讲什么 鬼魂棒球选手的
It's about ghost baseball players.
我觉得那很傻
I think it's stupid.
所以现在他为了 那部傻电影 生我的气了
So, now he's all mad at me about the stupid movie.
他是因为你不听他说话而生气
Robin, he's upset because you wouldn't listen to him,
不是因为你不喜欢那部电影
not because you didn't like some movie.
怎么能有人不喜欢梦幻之地?
How do you not like Field of Dreams?!
倾听是一段感情的基础
Listening is the foundation of a relationship.
如果他真的一直嘀咕
And if he's really droning on,
你可以练习倒着说字母表
you can always practice saying the alphabet backwards.
以防酒后驾车被警察逮到
You know, in case you get pulled over for a DUI.
我想我不需要练习那个
I guess I don't know how to do that.
就算你是清醒的 那也很难
Yeah, it's really hard, even when you're sober.
我就是这么和警察解释的
That's what I tried to explain to the cop.
我不知道 怎么处理这种 "女朋友该做的事"
No, I mean, I guess I don't know how to do this girlfriend thing.
我从来没有过这么认真的交往过
I've never been in a relationship this serious before.
我是不是应该去跟他道歉?
I  should probably go tell him I'm sorry, shouldn't I?
你现在就在倒背  对吧?
You're trying to do it right now, aren't you?
Q前面到底是什么?
What the hell comes before "Q"?
电影结束的时候 他和父亲又玩了一次 接抛球
Then at the end of the movie when he has a catch with his dad, like...
就像他以前年轻 时候都没玩过一样
like he never did when he was young enough for it to matter.
我们能谈点别的吗?
Can we talk about something else?
知道吗  伙计
You know what, dude?
忘了罗宾吧 你今晚和我们混了
Forget about Robin, okay? You're hanging with us tonight.
我有个超棒的派对在等着呢
I've got an awome party lined up.
上帝啊
Oh, God.
又是个古怪的全男人派对吗?
This gonna be another one of your weird all-guy parties?
那是个扑克牌游戏 你到底有什么毛病啊?
That was a poker game. What is wrong with you?
不  那是今年第一个法学院派对
No, it's the first law school party of the year
那肯定会很棒
and it's gonna be awesome.
自从去年我和莉莉分手后
I haven't seen this guys since, like, last year
我已经很久没见过他们了
before Lily and I broke up.
所以我得向所有人 宣布这个消息
So I'm gonna have to break the news to everybody.
那肯定会让他们伤心的
It's really gonna bum them out.
这个派对肯定会很糟
This party's gonna suck.
这个派对我很乐意参加
Well, love to join you at that one.
但是我有性感拳击的票子
But I got tickets to Foxy Boxing.
我也想和你们一起玩 但我要回去
I wish I could join you guys, but I got to get back
完成我明显很无聊的工作
to my apparently boring job.
- 你的工作不无聊啊 - 罗宾觉得无聊
- Your job's not boring. - Robin thinks so.
伙计  很多美女认为建筑师很酷
Dude, lots of chicks think architects are hot.
想想看  你能凭空制作东西出来
Think about it, you create something out of nothing.
这就像是上帝
You're like God.
没人比上帝更帅了
There's nobody hotter than God.
很高兴你能引用圣经
I love it when you quote Scripture.
我是说  你应该对女士们 使用你的建筑师魅力
I'm telling you, you should use the architect angle with the ladies.
首先  我已经有女朋友了
Okay, first of all, I have a girlfriend.
再说  建筑师魅力根本对她无效
Second, the architect angle doesn't even work on her.
第三  我不觉得那会 对任何人有效永远
And, third, I can't imagine that working on anyone ever.
那是因为你总是这样...
That's 'cause you're always like...
泰德・莫斯比  建筑师
Ted Mosby, architect.
如果是我  我会这样...
If it were me, I'd be like...
泰德・莫斯比  建筑师
Ted Mosby, architect.
只要说的语气对 任何东西听起来 都会印象深刻
Anything sounds impressive when it's said with the right attitude.
马修・埃里克森
Marshall Ericksen.
最近刚被甩 现在正要去一个很糟的派对
Recently dumped and heading to a lame party.
女士们  别激动
Whoa. Whoa, ladies, please take it easy.
你们每个人都能得到我
There's enough of me for everyone.
嗨  你好
Oh. Hi. Hello.
好了  我们要走了...
All right. We're gonna take off..
等等  我和你们一起走
Wait up, I'll leave with you guys.
泰德・莫斯比  建筑师
Ted Mosby, architect.
相信我
Trust  me.
只是有点好奇
Hey, just out of curiosity.
如果有人告诉你 他是个建筑师
If  a guy told you he was an architect,
你会怎么想?
what would you think of that?
你开玩笑吗?
Are you kidding?
建筑师很酷
Architects are hot.
你觉得布莱迪先生是怎么约到卡罗尔的? (美国电影脱线家族里布莱迪是建筑师)
How do you think Mr. Brady scored a babe like Carol?
很好的观点
Solid point.
她的确是有一头金发
She did have hair of gold.
对  是有
- Yes, she did. - Mm-hmm.
泰德还在这儿吗?
Hey, Carl, is Ted still here?
不在
No.
莉莉
Hey, Lily.
- 你还是单身吗? - 对
- You still single? - Yes.
知道吗...这些年来 我给了你很多免费的饮料
You know... I've poured a lot of free drinks for you over the years.
很多
A lot.
你真的会和一个为了啤酒
Carl, do you really want to be with a woman
跟人上床的女人在一起?
who would trade sex for beer?
如果是你  就会
Only if you're into it.
我请你
It's on me.
谢谢
Thanks.
泰德去哪儿了
I wonder where Ted went.
泰德・莫斯比 那个建筑师?
Ted Mosby, the architect?
非常正确
Actually, yeah.
他是个非常酷的男人
Oh, he is such a cool guy.
他刚才还在这儿
He was here earlier.
是什么让你决定 要成为一名建筑师的?
And what made you decide you wanted to become an architect?
艺术家的灵魂
Well, you know, soul of an artist,
大师级精湛的手艺
hands of a master craftsman.
我想这是不可避免的
It was inevitable, I guess.
我肯定你会画画  对吗?
I bet you can draw, can't you?
你应该画画我
You should draw me.
我可以试试 但我怕你最后变成 一个中世纪的3层结构
Well, I could try, but you might end up looking like a midcentury tri-level.
如果你愿意我的朋友马修 邀请我去一个派对  我们可以一起去
Hey. If you want, my friend Marshall invited me to this party we could all go to.
马修也很棒  虽然只是个律师
Marshall's great. He's just a lawyer,
但是总要有人 帮我们这种创作型的人把纸放好吧
but somebody has to push the paper around for us creative types.
- 我说的没错吧 - 没错
- Am I right? - Yeah.
-他邀请她去了派对 -天啊 你还好吗?
He asked her to a party. Oh, my God, are you okay?
好啊  这很好 这样对我们都好
Okay? It's awesome. It's a win-win.
泰德找到发泄的地方 我又不用再听他讲
Ted got to vent and I don't have to hear it.
也许他唆完之后就会回来
Maybe after he's done with the talkie-talk, he'll come over
然后我们就可以开始有趣的部分了
and I'll get the fun part.
你有毛病吗?
What is wrong with you?
天啊  我觉得教你谈恋爱 像是在说外星话
God, I feel like I'm teaching love as a second language here.
你知道当你的男朋友向你诉苦时
Okay, you know how when he tells you boring work stories
你应该要倾听了
you're supposed to listen?
那么  当他在酒吧 随便约了个女孩去派对的时候
Well, when he picks up some random girl at a bar,
你应该要感到害怕
you're supposed to freak out.
我才不害怕呢 我觉得她肯定很胖
I'm not freaking out because in my mind, she's fat.
她是健身拳击的教练
She's a kickboxing instructor.
她的屁股比我的脸还好看
Her ass looks better than my face.
好吧  我们改去派对吧
All right, we'll swing by the party.
这个派对是为了马修一些
Now the party was for some of Marshall's classmates
从哥伦比亚法学院来的同学办的
from Columbia Law School,
这些人在白天是全国最尖锐
who by day were some of the sharpest
思想最严肃的人
and most serious young legal minds in the country.
但是到了晚上...
By night, however...
该死  这儿都是些 快喝醉的准律师
Damn, these are some drunk almost-lawyers.
说真的...
Okay! Seriously...
谁想要刮我的屁股
who wants to shave my ass?!
这家伙后来变成了 最高法院检察官
That guy went on to become a Supreme Court justice.
那些家伙和他们勾搭的女人在哪儿?
Okay, where are the guys and the hooker?
你们好啊  女士们 欢迎来这个派对
Yo, what's up, ladies? Welcome to the party. Yeah!
只需在这里签上你们的名字 表示同意这里的主人
Just need you to sign this release protecting the host
不用对某位或是所有人 有可能的自我伤害行为负责
from any and all responsibility should you harm yourself
或是第三方的行为负责
or a third party.
然后就尽情狂欢吧
Then freakin' rage! Yeah!
醉了的法律人士 你有见过马修・埃里克森吗?
Hey, drunk legal dude, um... have you seen Marshall Ericksen?
他和一个叫泰德的人在一起
He was with a guy named Ted.
泰德・莫斯比 那个建筑师?
You mean Ted Mosby, the architect?
真是个梦想家！
Man, what a visionary.
没错  他们刚才在这儿
Yeah, they were here.
获奖的确很棒 它们很配我的架子
Awards are nice, they look good on my shelf.
没有什么称赞比得上
But none of that acclaim means anything compared to the joy
看到太阳从你设计的 第一幢楼前冉冉升起的快乐
of seeing the sun rise over your first building.
Wow.
我很乐意和你一起看日出
I would love to watch the sun rise with you.
我知道  你会的
I know you would.
这可是个工作
It's the job.
你今晚应该让我们刮你的屁股
Dude. You should let us shave your ass tonight.
没门
No way.
马修  莉莉在哪儿?
Hey, Marshall, where's Lily?
我不想这么早毁了大家的派对
I didn't want to ruin the party for everybody this early, but, uh...
但是  大家都请坐
everyone take a seat.
莉莉今年夏天取消了原定的婚礼
Um... Lily actually called off the wedding this summer
去了旧金山
to go to San Francisco.
所以...
So...
我们分手了
we're broken up.
她的名字不在租约上吧?
Her name wasn't on your lease, was it?
如果没有的话  根据纽约洲的法律 你没有义务
'Cause if not, New York state law, you're not obligated
在你搬的时候要给她一半的定金
to give her half the deposit when you move.
那不是我真正担心的部分
Yeah, that's not really the part I was worried about, guys.
不要忘了史密斯・罗赛贝特 74年的案例
And don't forget the precedent set by Smith v. Rosenblatt, '74.
她所有留在你房子里的东西
Any personal effects she left in your house or dwelling
过了30天后就是你的了
become yours after 30 days.
我们能不能暂时不要 用律师的观点来看
Guys, can we cease and desist with the lawyer speak for a minute?
爱已死
Love died.
那个让你陷入爱河的爱 它现在已经死了
The love that made you all believe in love, that's dead now.
你应该起诉她
You should sue her.
真的吗? 为了什么呢  凯拉?
Uh, really? On what ground, Kara?
理由就是...闭嘴
On the grounds of... shut up.
那是我们的法律代理人
That's our attorney general.
看到吗?马修还陷在我们 分手问题上
See? Marshall's still hung up on our breakup.
为什么? 因为我都听他说话
Why? Because I listened to him.
那是段坚定  稳固的感情
It was a strong and nurturing relationship
而我把它当旧口香糖似的抛弃了
that I threw away like old gum.
我不是在担心什么 不过  说回泰德的"日出"
Not that I'm worried or anything, but, um, back to the sun rising
用什么话形容她最贴切的?
over Ted and, uh... oh, what tasteful way did you describe her?
那个姑娘有个超棒的臀部
The girl with the smackable ass.
没错  就是那位年轻女士
Yes, that's the young lady.
我认识个电音俱乐部的保安
So,  I know the bouncer at this techno club, Posers.
你想和我一起去跳舞吗?
Do you feel like dancing?
很好  泰德不可能会去跳舞的
Yeah, okay. There is no way Ted went dancing.
泰德讨厌俱乐部
Ted hates clubs.
当然  我喜欢俱乐部
Hell, yeah. I love clubs.
虽然我今晚应该要设计大教堂
I mean, I was going to design a cathedral tonight,
我要解开上帝和人类之间的关系
kind of take a whack at the whole relationship between God and man conundrum.
但是没问题  我们去跳舞吧
But sure, let's go dancing.
等等  我和我朋友说一声
Wait, let me just check with my friend.
好的
Okay.
你想去一个超级吵闹 不断重复放些
Hey, Marshall. You up for some super loud, repetitive music
从90年代中期就没变过 音乐的地方吗？
that hasn't changed since the mid-90s?
当然要去了
Um... only always.
走吧
Let's go.
跳舞?他和个女孩去跳舞?
Dancing? He went dancing with this girl?
也许这就不太好了
Okay, maybe this is a little bad.
跳舞太糟了 跳完就该上床了
Dancing is bad. Dancing leads to sex.
你终于从自由之城成长了吗?
Did you grow up in that Footloose town?
我要打给他 我要告诉他我错了
I'm calling him. I'm telling him that I was wrong
我很抱歉  而且 我非常想听他那些愚蠢的故事
and I'm sorry, and I totally want to listen to his stupid stories.
想个别的方法来说 你会没事的...
Yeah, think of another way to phrase that and you'll be fine.
他不接电话
He's not answering.
打给马修
Calling Marshall.
喂
Hello.
马修  我是罗宾 我能和泰德说话吗?
Marshall, hi, it's Robin. Can I talk to Ted?
罗比  你好啊
Oh, Robin, hi.
不  泰德今晚不在这儿 他...他在工作
Um, no, Ted's not here tonight. He's, uh... he's working.
好的 再见
Uh, okay. Bye.
马修在骗我
Marshall just lied.
泰德出轨了
Ted's cheating on me.
不好意思  我要找一对 早些时候来过这儿的两个男人
Excuse me. I'm looking for a couple guys who came in here earlier.
一个大约6英尺4英寸 重210磅 浅棕色头发
One's about six-four, 210, sandy brown hair.
还有一个是出轨的混蛋
And the other's a cheating bastard.
你需要更新一下我的记忆
You're going to need to refresh my memory.
好的  小伙子 我们知道规矩
Okay, fella, baby knows how this game's played.
20美金能帮你想起来吗?
How's a $20 help your memory?
谢谢  但是说真的 今晚太疯狂了
Thanks,  but seriously, it was crazy tonight.
你真的应该更新一下我的记忆
You really do need to refresh my memory.
那我能不能...?
Then can I have the...?
没关系  你留着吧
That's cool. You keep that.
我们要找的人是个建筑师
So these guys-- one of them's an architect.
泰德・莫斯比 那个建筑师?
Ted Mosby, the architect?
就是他
That's the one.
对 他来过这里
Oh, yeah, he was here.
然后我说  不  弗兰克・杰瑞 这次你把自己黑了
And then I was all, "No, Frank Gehry. You're on your own this time."
这就是那个黑客最后的职业生涯
And that, my dear, was the end of that hack's career.
我就住在街对面
I live across the street.
那可真是出人意料
That is one hell of a non sequitur.
你想去坐一会儿?
You want to come over?
我还不确定
Well, I don't know.
但至少我应该送你回家
But I suppose I should at least give you a ride home.
跳上来
Hop on.
我们一会儿在书吧见  温尼
I'll see you at book club, Vinny.
- 我会给你带三明治的 - 太棒了
- Yeah. I'll be bringing the crudite. - Nice.
兄弟  兄弟  你这是干什么?
Dude, dude, what are you doing?
奔跑啊
Galloping.
你已经证实了建筑师 泰德・莫斯比 确实能泡到妞
You proved it, all right? The whole Ted Mosby, architect things works.
建筑师法则
Architects rule! Whoo-hee!
你真的一点也不担心有人
Aren't you a little worried that a certain somebody
可能会发现你现在所作所为?
might find out that you're doing this?
这不是你  泰德
This isn't you, Ted.
今天就是这样
It is tonight.
Whoo!
你认识这个女的 她住哪儿?
You know this girl. Where does she live?
你至少要给我20块 不然我不会告诉你的
I'm not telling you that for less than 20 bucks.
- 我没钱了 - 我也是
- Well, I'm out of money. - I'm cashed, too.
你的手袋我也收
I'll take your purse.
我的手袋?
My purse?
我女朋友喜欢clutche的东西
Yeah, my girl likes clutches.
好吧  给你
Okay, fine.
你要告诉她 这个和巧克力色靴子很配
You should tell her that looks really good with a chocolate boot.
你该庆幸我带的是我最小的手袋
Bitch is lucky I brought my small purse.
没地方能放我的枪  给你
No room for my gun. Here.
快说  那个荡妇住哪里?
Now where does the rodeo slut live?
那个亮绿灯的大楼 3楼C座
The building with the green light, apartment 3-C.
我的天啊  罗宾
Oh, my God, Robin,
你是不是要狠狠揍她一顿
are you going to kick this girl's ass?
没错
Yeah...
还要偷了她的手袋
and steal her purse.
真不敢相信 他竟然背着我偷情
I can't believe he's cheating on me.
你知道我有多少次这样的机会?
You know how many times I could have cheated?
6...不 7次
Six... no seven.
如果你知道其中的两个是谁 你会很惊讶的
And you know two of them, and they would surprise you.
3楼C座  开始吧 你准备好了?
3-C, let's do this. You ready?
我是不是应该踢门进去?
Should I just kick the door in?
这双高跟鞋真的很好看 你的手袋已经没了...
Those are really nice heels and you already lost the purse.
看看门有没有锁
Let's see if it's unlocked.
没锁
It's unlocked.
好吧  我们进去 狠狠踹她屁股一脚
Okay, get in there and kick some spankable ass.
罗宾
Robin.
- 有问题的是我 - 什么?
- I'm the problem. - What?
你说得对
You were right.
我不知道怎么做女朋友
I don't know how to be a girlfriend.
我找到了世界上最好的男人
I took the nicest guy in the world
却把他弄成了个爱情骗子
and I made him a cheater.
别光站在这儿贬低你自己
Well, don't stand out here and beat yourself up.
进去揍泰德一顿
Get in there and beat Ted up.
我来处理那个下贱的自由搏击手
I'll handle the slutty kickboxer.
事实上  我还是处理泰德吧
Actually, I'll take Ted.
- 我们开始吧 - 我来了
- Let's do this. - Bring it.
你知道你在干...
What do you think you're...?
巴尼?
Barney?
谢天谢地  你们来了 能帮我解开吗?我没有指甲
Thank God you're here. Can you help with this? I need nails.
我现在完全糊涂了 泰德在哪儿?
Okay, I'm totally lost here. Where's Ted?
泰德?他在工作啊
Ted? He's at work.
你怎么会在这儿的?
How did you get here?
好棒的故事  像往常一样
Awesome story. As per usual.
你觉得布莱迪先生 是怎么约到卡罗尔的?
How do you think Mr. Brady scored a babe like Carol?
很好的观点
Solid point.
- 而且她确实有一头金发 - 对 没错
- And she did have hair of gold. - Yes, she did.
对不起  我忘了我的 我忘了看性感拳击赛的望远镜了
Sorry, I forgot my binocs for Foxy Boxing.
看来这里有更性感的东西嘛
Whoo, looks like things just got a little foxier right here.
没错  是有 而且你来得正好
Yes, they did. And you're just in time.
姑娘们  我要走了 但是我留下个好货 只要你们不嫌脏
Girls, I got to go, but I'm leaving you in very good, if slightly sullied hands.
不要走  我们还不知道你的名字 怎么知道哪座楼是你设计的
Don't go. We don't even know your name to look out for your buildings.
对啊 别走 (快走)
Yeah, stay.
请稍等一下
Excuse us for one second.
你说得没错 用建筑师的魅力真的有效
Okay, you were right-- the architect thing totally works.
但是我已经有女朋友了 而且我现在要回去工作了
But I've got a girlfriend and I've got to get back to work.
这个工程越来越难做了(暗指抛唇ㄖ越来越硬了)
This project is getting harder and harder.
- 讲得好 - 谢谢
- Yeah, you did. - Yeah, had to.
再见
See ya.
对不起  我的... 实习生必须要走了
Sorry, my, uh... intern had to leave.
太可惜了
Oh, well, that's too bad.
对了  我是安娜
I'm Anna, by the way.
泰德・莫斯比 建筑师
Ted Mosby... architect.
但是没有一种称赞能和那种
But  none of that acclaim means anything compared to the joy
看着太阳在你的处女作那儿 冉冉升起的快乐相比
of seeing the sun rise over your first building.
- 兄弟  兄弟  你这是干什么? - 奔跑
- Dude, dude, what are you doing? - Galloping.
你已经证实了用泰德・莫斯比 建筑师 确实能泡到妞
All right, you proved it. The whole Ted Mosby, architect thing works.
建筑师法则
Architects rule! Whoo-hoo.
你真的一点也不担心有人 可能会发现你现在所作所为吗?
Aren't you afraid a certain somebody might find out about this?
这不是你 泰德
I mean, this isn't you, Ted.
今天是...
It is tonight.
接下来的几个小时
And that led to a couple of hours
作为一名绅士 我不能  告诉你
that I cannot, as a gentleman, divulge to you.
我们在这儿  这儿 还有这儿做了
We did it right here, and here and here.
但是你为什么要用泰德的名字?
But why would you use Ted's name?
我最近在互联网上有点坏名声
I've had some recent bad press on the World Wide Web.
所有我对用真名有点顾虑
So I'm taking a T.O. on the whole "using my real name" thing.
太好了  根本不是泰德 什么问题都没了
Oh, this is great. It wasn't Ted. Everything's okay.
并不是没问题了
Everything isn't okay.
看看我  我像个疯子似的 嫉妒而且还在乱想
Look at me. I'm acting crazy and jealous and paranoid.
人们谈恋爱的时候就是这样的
This is how people act in relationships.
那就是我不想陷入感情的原因
And that's why I avoid relationships.
知道吗
Well, guess what,
我已经好几个月没有发疯 嫉妒或是乱想了
I haven't been crazy or jealous or paranoid in months,
我真的很想那样
and I really miss it.
这一段的结尾就是 让我们在巴尼一夜情的房间里
And thus ended this chapter of, "Let's pour our hearts out
互诉心房吧
in the bedroom of Barney's one-night stand."
快点我们要在 她洗完澡前离开
Come on, let's go before she gets out of the shower.
你真是头猪 你甚至不打算说声再见吗?
You're such a pig. You're not even going to say good-bye?
正如你们所见 我写了封公式信
I'll have you know I composed a lovely form letter
专门为了在这种情况下用的
for use in just such an occasion.
只要填上名字  然后...
Just fill out her name and then...
好像是有个A的
Something with a "A."
A... A...
我就写"公民"吧
I'll just put "resident."
撤  撤  撤  撤
Go, go, go, go.
罗宾那晚走了很久
Robin took a long walk that night.
她思考着怎么 向另一个人敞开胸怀
She thought about how opening yourself up to another person
通常放开胸怀意味着 变得有点疯狂
usually means opening yourself up to going a little crazy.
她想了如果一个人的话 会更容易些
She thought about how much easier it was just to be alone.
然后她来见了我
And then she came to see me.
# And I am nothing of a builder #
# But here I dreamt I was an architect... # Hey.
Hey.
- 你来这儿干嘛? - 我带了点唐纳兹(甜面包圈)
- What are you doing here? - I brought donuts.
我不是吹牛 他们放了很多果酱
And I don't want to brag, but they're filled with jelly.
谢谢
Thanks.
那么...你今晚怎么样?
So, uh... how was your night?
还...不错 没什么特别的
It was... fine. Nothing exciting.
你呢?
How was yours?
你真的想听无聊 建筑师的事情吗?
You really want to hear about boring architect stuff?
是的  我想听
Yes, I do.
之前的事我很抱歉
I'm sorry about earlier.
我根本没看完过梦幻之地
To tell you the truth, I never even saw all of Field of Dreams.
我看到一半就睡着了
I fell asleep half way through.
什么?最后20分钟是精华部分
What? The best part's the last 20 minutes.
也许他们应该把那部分提前一点 因为...
Well, maybe they should have moved that part up a little bit earlier, 'cause...
知道吗?
You know what, um...
我想说的是
What I'm trying to say is...
我喜欢当你的"垃圾桶"
I love being the person you bitch to.
今天过得怎么样? 建筑师先生
So how was your day, Mr. Architect?
我喜欢你那样说话
Oh, I like the way you say that.
你想看看那座大楼吗？
Hey, you want to see the building
那会让斯普肯所有的男人 觉得自己不够大
that will make every man in Spokane feel inadequate?
很明显
Obviously.
- 哇 - 没错吧
- Wow. - Yeah.
你没提到底边那圈叶子
You know, you didn't mention all the foliage around the base.
如果能修修底部 剩下的看起来会更大
If you trim that back, the rest would look bigger.
你不用告诉我
You don't have to tell me.
还有...纯粹为了好玩... 我已经
And, um... just for fun, I've...
我做了我理想中的建筑的图纸
I've sort of been working on my own idea of what I think the building should be.
你觉得怎么样?
What do you think?
还记得第一次去斯普肯 我指给你们看的那栋摩天楼?
You know that time we went to Spokane and I pointed out that skyscraper?
那是我的第一件设计品
That was the first building I ever designed.
而那天晚上是我第一次 把我的手稿给别人看
And that night was the first time I showed anyone my first drawing of it.
Wow.
泰德  这太棒了
Ted, this is amazing.
谢谢
Thanks.
也许并不会真的建成
It's not like it will ever come to anything.
那我就不知道了
I don't know.
但是有些事是可能的
It might come to something.
姑娘们都认为建筑师非常帅
You know, girls find architects very hot.
好的
Okay,
不过你可不要期望什么 "78层"或别的东西(暗指"别指望他的那啥能有那么长")
but I don't want you expecting 78 stories or anything.
亲爱的公民
"Dear Resident...
我们一起度过的时光 不管多久
The time we spent together, however long it was,
对我来说都是我的全部
meant the world to me.
我很愿意再一次见你 但是很不幸  我不能
I would love to see you again, but unfortunately, I cannot.
要知道  我是个鬼魂
You see, I am a ghost.
我只能每10年 在我死祭的那天
I can't only materialize once every decade
成形一次
on the anniversary of my death.
在我活着的这天 我选择和你一起度过
I chose to spend my one day among the living with you,
亲爱的  公民
sweet... Resident.
也许我们会在 下一个10年再次见面
Perhaps we will meet again in another decade,
到那时一定要保持 你现在的身材
provided you keep your figure.
给你我来自远方的爱
Until then, all my love from the beyond.
巴尼
Barney."
巴尼？
Barney?
这该死的巴尼是谁?
Who the hell is Barney?